注:
本段出自T&J E26 Solid Serenade（无尽小夜曲）
根据wikia上的信息 tomandjerry.wikia.com/wiki/Is_You_Is_or_Is_You_Ain%27t_My_Baby
歌手并非原唱Louis Jordan 而是Ira Woods
我的宝贝总是姗姗来迟
I got a gal who's always late
每次约会都是如此
Any time we have a date
翻译 时间轴 压制：Bolshevik0
可我爱她
But I love her
我要问个明白
I'm gonna ask her
你到底还是不是我的心肝宝贝
Is you is or is you ain't my baby
你的行为让我迟疑
Way you're acting lately makes me doubt
你依旧是我的宝贝
You is still my baby, baby
可你对我的热情大不如以前
Seems my flame in your heart's done gone out
女人总是让人猜不透
A woman is a creature that has always been strange
每当你认为你参透了
Just when you're sure of what you'll find
她就开始玩新的花样
She's gone and made a change
你到底还是不是我的心肝宝贝
Is you is or is you ain't my baby
也许我的宝贝有了新欢
Maybe baby's found somebody new
也许你依旧是我的宝贝
My baby is still my baby true
你到底还是不是我的心肝宝贝
Is you is or is you ain't my baby
也许我的宝贝有了新欢
Maybe baby's found somebody new
也许你依旧是我的宝贝
Or is my baby still my baby true